Sam Wang Shusen

Software Engineer at Fuji Xerox Software Center Singapore

wlgq@hotmail.com

Summary

Hi, my name is Sam, a Java and JavaScript stack developer with 5 years work experience.

As a fulll-time employed enginerr, I use Java EE and frontend framework to deliver high quality products.

At free time, I contribute to open source projects to broaden experience and skills.

Also sometimes, I write blog to share my ideas.

Github: https://github.com/shuson/ Blog: http://www.nevermoi.com/

Experience

Software Engineer at Fuji Xerox Singapore Software Center

January 2015 - Present (1 year 11 months)

- 1. Research in frontend integrated system, using Webpack, NPM, Gulp, etc.
- 2. Design and develop frontend Single Page Application using MVVM frameworks, i.e. React, Vue, etc.
- 3. Develop Cloud Service customized SDK using techniques Java EE, OSGi, OAuth2, Odata, etc.

Software Engineer at CrimsonLogic

September 2013 - January 2015 (1 year 5 months)

- 1. Get involved into ³/₄ SDLC from system design, and take participate into a Content Management System design and implementation by working with BPAs and Test team.
- 2. Lead the development of a module, which integrates data processing, business workflow management and responsive web presentation.
- 3. Code and test web based application using JavaEE framework, Spring, Hibernate and frontend presentation technologies like, jQuery, Bootstrap, Ajax with Eclipse and Maven.

Technical Consultant at SharePointBoost

August 2011 - July 2012 (1 year)

- 1. Proactively communicate and collaborate with Sales/Marketing team and vendors for requirements gathering
- 2. Deliver original product design and prototype
- 3. Provide technical support and trouble shooting for customer.

Education

National University of Singapore

Graduate Diploma, System Analysis, 2012 - 2013

China Agricultural University

Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology, 2006 - 2010

Skills & Expertise

Java

JavaScript

Software Design

Linux

Python

Web Services

RESTful architecture

AngularJS

AJAX

Nginx

OAuth

OSGi

Languages

Chinese (Native or bilingual proficiency)

English (Professional working proficiency)